let questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "I hope that the truth ___ very soon",
        answer: "will be found out",
        options: [
            "will be finding out",
            "will be found out",
            "will find out",
            "is found out"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 2,
        question: "Did the company test the equipment yesterday? Yes it _____.",
        answer :"was tested",
        options: [
            "was tested",
            "has tested",
            "had tested",
            "tested"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 3,
        question: " The sports competitions which ___ on Sunday ___ by a lot of people.",
        answer: "will be held / will be visited",
        options: [
            "will held / will visit",
            "was held / will visit",
            "will be held / will be visited",
            "are held / will be visited"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 4,
        question: " This story ___ to everybody as the name of the first space pioneer ___ in the heart of people all over the world.",
        answer: "is known / lives",
        options: [
            "is known / lives",
            "knew / lived",
            "knows / lives",
            "is known / is lived"
        ]
    },

    {
        number: 5,
        question: "Donâ€™t touch the door, it ___ just ___ .",
        answer: "has / been painted",
        options: [
            "is / painted",
            "has / been painted",
            "is / being painted",
            "had / be painted"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: "By the time we came to the bookshop all books ___",
        answer: "had been sold",
        options: [
            "had been sold",
            "is being sold",
            "are being sold",
            "are sold"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: "I ___ that I ___ at the station at 5.",
        answer: "was told / should be met",
        options: [
            " told / is being met",
            " am told / was met",
            "will be told / would be met",
            "was told / should be met"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: "Many modern apartments ___ in Berlin since 1980.",
        answer: "have been built",
        options: [
            "has been built",
            "are building",
            "have been built",
            "are built"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: "Everything ___ before you came",
        answer: "had been done",
        options: [
            "has been done",
            "had been done",
            "has done",
            "was done"
        ]
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: " Last Monday I received a telegram ___ by my sister on the 1st of May.",
        answer: "sent",
        options: [
            "had sent",
            "was sent",
            "sent",
            "sending"
        ]
    },
]